Narrator: Grace
Interviewer: Have you bought anything from a chain store recently?
Grace: Yes, I have.
I went to H&M three weeks ago.
Interviewer: And what did you buy?
Grace: I bought a skirt.
It’s a long, black skirt.
Interviewer: Are you happy with it?
Grace: Yes, yes, and, er…
it was very cheap because it was in the sale.
And it suits me.
Narrator: Emilia
Interviewer: Have you been shopping for clothes recently?
Emilia: Yes, I went shopping at the weekend with my friends.
Interviewer: Where did you go?
Emilia: We went to the city centre, to Princes Street,
that’s where we always go.
Interviewer: Did you buy anything?
Emilia: I tried on a few things in Zara,
but in the end there wasn’t anything I liked.
The only thing I bought was a new case for my phone in the Apple store.
I really like it.
Narrator: Leo
Interviewer: Have you ever bought anything from Uniqlo?
Leo: Sure, I often buy stuff on their website.
Interviewer: What was the last thing you bought from them?
Leo: I got some T-shirts a few weeks ago.
I always get them there.
Interviewer: How many did you get?
Leo: Three…or was it four?
No, it was three.
Interviewer: And are you happy with them?
Leo: Yes.
I like their T-shirts
and they were good value –
about £15.00 each.